<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="splash_image">Splash image</string>
    <string name="splash_welcome_message">Welcome in Egypt</string>
    <string name="tab_historical_places_fragment_title">Historical Places</string>
    <string name="tab_public_places_fragment_title">Public Places</string>
    <string name="tab_favorite_dishes_fragment_title">Favorite Dishes</string>
    <string name="tab_hotels_fragment_title">Hotels</string>

    <!-- Historical places title text-->
    <string name="historical_places_title_1">The Great Pyramid of Giza </string>
    <string name="historical_places_title_2">Egyptian Museum </string>
    <string name="historical_places_title_3">Pyramid of Djoser </string>
    <string name="historical_places_title_4">Citadel of Salah El Din </string>
    <string name="historical_places_title_5">Mosque of Muhammad Ali </string>
    <string name="historical_places_title_6">Mosque of Ibn Tulun </string>
    <string name="historical_places_title_7">The Hanging Church </string>

    <!-- Historical places address text-->
    <string name="historical_places_address_1">Giza City, Giza, Greater Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="historical_places_address_2">Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="historical_places_address_3">Al Giza Desert, Giza , Egypt</string>
    <string name="historical_places_address_4">Salah Salem St, El-Darb El-Ahmar, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
    <string name="historical_places_address_5">Salah Salem St, El-Darb El-Ahmar, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
    <string name="historical_places_address_6">Tolon, El-Sayeda Zainab, Cairo Governorate</string>
    <string name="historical_places_address_7">Kom Ghorab, Old Cairo, Cairo Governorate</string>

    <!-- Historical places description text-->
    <string name="historical_places_description_1">The Great Pyramid of Giza (also known as the Pyramid of Khufu or the Pyramid of Cheops) is the oldest and largest of the three pyramids in the Giza pyramid complex bordering present-day Giza in Greater Cairo, Egypt. It is the oldest of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World, and the only one to remain largely intact. </string>
    <string name="historical_places_description_2">The Museum of Egyptian Antiquities, known commonly as the Egyptian Museum or Museum of Cairo, in Cairo, Egypt, is home to an extensive collection of ancient Egyptian antiquities. It has 120,000 items, with a representative amount on display, the remainder in storerooms. Built in 1901 by the Italian construction company Garozzo-Zaffarani to a design by the French architect Marcel Dourgnon, the edifice is one of the largest museums in the region. As of March 2019, the museum is open to the public. In 2020 the museum is due to be superseded by the new Grand Egyptian Museum at Giza.</string>
    <string name="historical_places_description_3">The Pyramid of Djoser (or Djeser and Zoser), or Step Pyramid (kbhw-ntrw in Egyptian[citation needed]), is an archaeological remain in the Saqqara necropolis, Egypt, northwest of the city of Memphis. The 6-tier, 4-sided structure is the earliest colossal stone building in Egypt. It was built in the 27th century BC during the Third Dynasty for the burial of Pharaoh Djoser. The pyramid is the central feature of a vast mortuary complex in an enormous courtyard surrounded by ceremonial structures and decoration. </string>
    <string name="historical_places_description_4">Citadel of Salah El Din is a medieval Islamic-era fortification in Cairo, Egypt, built by Salah ad-Din (Saladin) and further developed by subsequent Egyptian rulers. It was the seat of government in Egypt and the residence of its rulers for nearly 700 years from the 13th to the 19th centuries. Its location on a promontory of the Mokattam hills near the center of Cairo commands a strategic position overlooking the city and dominating its skyline. At the time of its construction, it was among the most impressive and ambitious military fortification projects of its time.</string>
    <string name="historical_places_description_5">Mosque of Muhammad Ali is a mosque situated in the Citadel of Cairo in Egypt and was commissioned by Muhammad Ali Pasha between 1830 and 1848.\n Situated on the summit of the citadel, this Ottoman mosque, the largest to be built in the first half of the 19th century, is, with its animated silhouette and twin minarets, the most visible mosque in Cairo. </string>
    <string name="historical_places_description_6">Mosque of Ibn Tulun is located in Cairo, Egypt. It is the oldest mosque in Egypt and Africa surviving in its full original form, and is the largest mosque in Cairo in terms of land area. Since Ibn Tulun Mosque has lots of open space, it brings in a lot of sun and shadows. It is built around an open square courtyard which allows natural light to travel through. Ibn Tulun Mosque features Samarra style- its decorations being created from carved stucco and wood.</string>
    <string name="historical_places_description_7">The Hanging Church is named for its location above a gatehouse of Babylon Fortress, the Roman fortress in Coptic Cairo (Old Cairo); its nave is suspended over a passage. The church is approached by twenty-nine steps; early travelers to Cairo dubbed it "the Staircase Church".</string>

    <!-- Public places title text-->
    <string name="public_places_title_1">Abdeen Palace </string>
    <string name="public_places_title_2">Cairo Opera House </string>
    <string name="public_places_title_3">Manial Palace and Museum </string>
    <string name="public_places_title_4">Baron Empain Palace </string>
    <string name="public_places_title_5">Al-Azhar Park </string>
    <string name="public_places_title_6">Cairo Tower </string>
    <string name="public_places_title_7">Tahrir Square </string>

    <!-- Public places address text-->
    <string name="public_places_address_1">El-Gomhoreya Square, Rahbet Abdin, Abdeen, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
    <string name="public_places_address_2">Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="public_places_address_3">1 Al Saraya, Old Cairo, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
    <string name="public_places_address_4">El-Orouba, El-Montaza, Heliopolis, Cairo Governorate</string>
    <string name="public_places_address_5">Salah Salem St, El-Darb El-Ahmar, Cairo Governorate, Egypt</string>
    <string name="public_places_address_6">Zamalek, Cairo Governorate</string>
    <string name="public_places_address_7">eltahrir sqair, Cairo Governorate</string>

    <!-- Public places description text-->
    <string name="public_places_description_1">Abdeen Palace is a historic Cairo palace, and one of the official residences and the principal workplace of the President of Egypt, located above Qasr el-Nil Street in eastern Downtown Cairo, Egypt. </string>
    <string name="public_places_description_2">The opera house was inaugurated on 10 October 1988. The funds for the complex were a gift from the nation of Japan to Egypt as a result of President Hosni Mubarak\'s visit to Japan in April 1983. Construction began in May 1985 and lasted for three years.</string>
    <string name="public_places_description_3">The palace and estate has been preserved as an Antiquities Council directed historic house museum and estate, reflecting the settings and lifestyle of the late 19th- and early 20th-century Egyptian royal prince and heir apparent. The residence compound, composed of five separate and distinctively styled buildings, is surrounded by Persian gardens within an extensive English Landscape garden estate park, along a small branch of the Nile.  </string>
    <string name="public_places_description_4">The palace was designed by French architect Alexandre Marcel and decorated by Georges-Louis Claude. Inspired by the Hindu temple of Angkor Wat in Cambodia, it was built between 1907 and 1911, in reinforced concrete. </string>
    <string name="public_places_description_5">Al-Azhar Park is listed as one of the world\'s sixty great public spaces by the Project for Public Spaces (PPS). The park was created by the Historic Cities Support Programme (HCSP) of the Aga Khan Trust for Culture (AKTC), an entity of the Aga Khan Development Network (AKDN). The park, developed at a cost in excess of USD $30 million. </string>
    <string name="public_places_description_6">Cairo Tower  is a free-standing concrete tower in Cairo, Egypt. At 187 m (614 ft), it has been the tallest structure in Egypt and North Africa for about 50 years. It was the tallest structure in Africa for ten years until 1971. </string>
    <string name="public_places_description_7">The square has been the location and focus for political demonstrations in Cairo, most notably those that led to the 2011 Egyptian revolution and the resignation of President Hosni Mubarak. </string>

    <!-- Favorite dishes title text-->
    <string name="favorite_dishes_title_1">Kushari </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_title_2">Ful medames </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_title_3">Om Ali </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_title_4">Feteer meshaltet </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_title_5">Hawawshi </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_title_6">Falafel </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_title_7">Basbousa </string>

    <!-- Favorite dishes address text-->
    <string name="favorite_dishes_address_1">Kushari Abu Tarek</string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_address_2">El Gahsh, El-Sayeda Zainab </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_address_3">El Malky, El-Sayeda Zainab </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_address_4">Wahet Omar, Km 111 Alexandria Desert Rd </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_address_5">Hawawshy Shalaby, saraya El Azbakeya St, DOWNTOWN. </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_address_6">El Gahsh, El-Sayeda Zainab </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_address_7">El Abd Pastry, Cairo Governorate</string>

    <!-- Favorite dishes description text-->
    <string name="favorite_dishes_description_1">An Egyptian dish that originated during the mid-19th century the dish combines Italian, Indian and Middle Eastern culinary elements. Kushari is made of rice, macaroni, and lentils mixed together, topped with a spiced tomato sauce and garlic vinegar and garnished with chickpeas and crispy fried onions and is often served with sprinklings of garlic juice, garlic vinegar and hot sauce are optional.  </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_description_2">Is a stew of cooked fava beans served with vegetable oil, cumin, and optionally with chopped parsley, garlic, onion, lemon juice, chili pepper and other vegetable, herb and spice ingredients. It is notably a staple food in Egypt.</string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_description_3">Is an Egyptian dessert. There are numerous variations with different composition. The name “Om Ali” is literally translated into the mother of Ali and it is traced back to the Ayyubid era. It is named after the wife of the ruler of the Ayyubid Empire in Egypt who used to make it for her husband.  </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_description_4">Is a flaky Egyptian layered pastry. It consists of many thin layers of dough and ghee and an optional filling. The fillings can be both sweet or savory. Sweet fillings may include cheese, coconut, mehalabiya, malban, nutella or chocolate, while savory fillings can be anything from ground beef to sausage or cheese. Plain feteer is usually soaked in honey and spread with jam or cheese or served with olives. Because of its versatility, feteer is often referred to as an Egyptian pizza. </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_description_5">Is a traditional Egyptian dish. It is a pita stuffed with minced meat and spiced with onions, pepper, parsley, and occasionally chilies. </string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_description_6">Is a deep-fried ball, or a flat or doughnut-shaped patty, made from ground chickpeas, fava beans, or both. Herbs, spices, and onion relatives are commonly added to the dough. It is a well-known Middle Eastern dish that most likely originated in Egypt.</string>
    <string name="favorite_dishes_description_7">Is a traditional Middle Eastern sweet cake that originated in Egypt. It is made from a semolina batter and sweetened with orange flower water or rose water simple syrup.  </string>

</resources>
